Contact

tracy0228.tl@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tracy-larkin-1b7374189 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Patient Safety
Quality Patient Care
Change Leadership

Tracy Larkin

Nurse Manager TriHealth MSN

Cincinnati, Ohio Area

Summary

Experienced Nursing Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Physician Relations, Teamwork, Healthcare Management, Patient Safety, and Quality Improvement. Strong healthcare services professional with a MSN focused in Nursing Administration from Mount St. Joseph University.

Experience

TriHealth

18 years 6 months

Nurse Manager

February 2012 - Present (8 years 5 months)

Patient Placement Specialist/ Supervisor

2010 - February 2012 (2 years)

Good Samaritan Hospital

Staff Registered Nurse, Charge Nurse, Clinical Coach January 2002 - 2010 (8 years)

Good Samaritan Hospital

Education

Mount St. Joseph University

MSN, Nursing Administration · (2015 - 2018)